No Other Choice is hands down the best international film of the year
here's why you have to watch it
from the South Korean auteur gave us Oldboy and Decision to Leave
Park Chan-wook's newest film
follows a father who has trouble finding a job
after being laid off from the paper industry
which leaves him No Other Choice but to eliminate the competition
and when I mean eliminate
I mean
eliminate
what I love about this movie
because this movie is a unique blend of dark humor
and social commentary
since Park Chan-wook is very intentional with his use of goofy comedy
as it helps emphasize the movie's profound themes
about the brutal struggles of unemployment
and the lengths we'll go to provide for our family
in such a hyper competitive world
and these messages are anchored through Lee Byung-hun's performance
who really takes control of the story with his own hands
it makes you empathize with a man who's doing unthinkable things
to escape unemployment and financially support his family
this movie is so good
that the Academy will have No Other Choice but to nominate this movie
and have No Other Choice
but to give Park Chan-wook the recognition he finally deserves
are you gonna watch it let me know your thoughts down below
because I give No Other Choice
a 9 / 10
which means